Guide to the Washington Area Women's Center records, 1868-1989 MS2344
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reprints, 1868, 1920, 1966-1980; 1966-1980; Series 5
  - Bart, Pauline; Depression in Middle Aged Women: Portnoy's Mother's Complaint; Sexism and Social Sciences: From the Gilded Cage to the Iron Cage...; Social Structure and Vocabularies of Discomfort: What Happened to Female Hysteria?; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Bassett, Marion; Let's Call Their Bluff - And Take Courage; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Beal, Frances; Double Jeopady: To Be Black and Female; D.C. Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Bem, Sandra L. and Daryl J. Bem; Sex-Segregated Want Ads: Do They Discourage Female Job Applicants?; Training the Woman to Know Her Place: The Power of a Nonconscious Ideology; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Bernstein, Judi, Peggy Morton, Linda Seese, Myrna Wood; Sisters, Brothers, Lovers … Listen!; Research Information Publications Project, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Blaisdell, Virginia; Freedom is a Long Time Comin', Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Blumenfeld, Warren; School is not a Gay Place to be (1971); Edcentric reprint, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Booth, Heather, Evi Goldfield, Sue Munaker; Towards a Radical Movement; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Borun, Minda, Molly McLaughlin, Gina Oboler, Norma Perchonock, Lorraine Sexton; Women's Liberation: An Anthropological View (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Brodsky, Annette M.; The Feminist Therapist Roster of the Association for Women in Psychology; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Broverman, Inge K., Donald M. Broverman, Frank E. Clarkson, Paul S. Rosenkrantz and Susan R. Vogel; Sex-Role Sterotypes and Clinical Judgements of Mental Health (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Linda; Canta una Mujer (1971); Athena Press, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Brown, William H. III; Sex Discrimination (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Bunch-Weeks, Charlotte; Asian Women in Revolution; A Broom of One's Own: Notes of a Women's Program; KNOW, Inc.. Washington Area Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Burris, Carol; A Feminist View of Problems in Childcare (1972); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Burton, Gabrielle; You, too, can walk on Water! (1972); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Cantarow, Ellen, Elizabeth Diggs, Katherine Ellis, Janet Marx, Lillian Robinson, Muriel Schein; Essay on Women's Liberation (1969); New University Conference Convention, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Cathey-Calvert, Carolyn; Sexism on Sesame Street: Outdated Concepts in a 'Progressive' Program; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Chase, Wilda; The Twig Benders; The Feminists, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Chesler, Phyllis; Marriage and Psychotherapy; The Radial Therapist, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Cisler, Lucinda; Abortion Law Repeal (sort of): A Warning to Women (1970); NYALR, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Clarenbach, Kathryn; Women Are People: Symposium on Behavorial Sciences (1969); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Clarkson, Frank, Susan R. Vogel, Inge K. Broverman, Donald M. Broverman, and Paul S. Rosenkrantz; Family Size and Sex-Role Sterotypes (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Cleary, Josephine; Notes from the Lower Classes II (1969); The Feminists, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Conrad-Rice, Joy Belle; Being Blonde and Hating It; Religion, Language, Psychology - Women Left Out; Something There is That Likes a Woman; Women: Take Your Men, Too!; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Courtney, Alice E. and Sarah Wernick Lockeretz; A Woman's Place: An Analysis of the Roles Portrayed by Women in Magazine Advertisements (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Cronan, Sheila; Marriage; The Feminists, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Dean, Heather; The Sexual Caste System (1966); Women's Liberation, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - dell'Olio, Anselma; Divisiveness and Self-Destruction in the Women's Movement: A Letter of Resignation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Densmore, Dana; Chilvalry - The Iron Hand in the Velvet Glove; Sex Roles and Female Oppression; Speech is the Form of Thought with a new glossary; Un Problema De Hombre: Ego Y Madruz; Without You and Within You; Who is Saying Men are the Enemy?; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Dinerman, Beatrice; Attitudes and Practices Toward Women in Architecture, Law, Engineering, Dentistry (1969); Women in Architecture; Sex Discrimination in Academia (1971); Sex Discrimination in the Legal Profession (1969); KNOW, Inc., 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Dixon, Marlene D.; A National Problem of Agitation and Struggle for the Women's Liberation Front of the New University Conference (1969); A Position Paper of Radical Women in the Profession: Or, Up From Ridicule; Why Women's Liberation (1969); 1969, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Dubois, Ellen; Struggling into Existence: The Feminism of Sarah and Angelina Grimke (1970); New England Free Press, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Dunbar, Roxanne; Female Liberation as the Basis for Social Revolution; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Dunn, Erica and Judy Klein; Women in the Russian Revolution (1970); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Eanet, Sue and Anne Goodman; An Article [ways in which working class women are affected by the militarization of American society], Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Edmiston, Susan; The Psychology of Day Care (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Edwards, Alison; Rape. Racism and the White Women's Movement: An Answer to susan Brownmiller; Sojourner Truth Organization, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Ehrenreich, Barbara; What is Socialist Feminism?; American Friends Service Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Eliasberg, Ann; Are You Hurting Your Daughter Without Knowing It?; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Ellinger, Mickey and John Rowntree; More on the Political Economy of Women's Liberation (1970); Bay Area Radical Education Project, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Farians, Elizabeth; The Human Dignity of Women in the Church (1967); The Status of Women in the Church (1968); Women in the Church Now (1968); KNOW, Inc., 1967-1968; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Faust, Jean; Words That Oppress (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Feminists, The; Organizational Principles and Structure; Statement of The Feminists on the Equal Rights Amendment (1970); The Feminists, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Fields, Rona M.; Public Education: Training for Sexism; The Taxonomy of Sexism (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Firestone, Shulamith; On Activism and the Media; Redstockings, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Fisher, Elizabeth; Anything You Can Do - An Answer to the Myth of the Vaginal Orgasm (1968); Children's Books, The Second Sex, Junior Division; KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Forefreedom, Ann; The Labrys of the Amazons (1973), Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Fraser, Clara; Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light (1980) The Emancipation of Women (1973); Response to "Notes on Leadership" (1975); Which Road Towards Women's Liberation: A Radical Vanguard or a Single-Issue Coalition?: Woman As Leader: Double Jeopardy on Account of Sex; Radical Women, 1973-1980; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Freeman, Jane and Marge Piercy; Getting Together: How to Start a Women's Liberation Group; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Freeman, Jo; The Building of the Gilded Cage; 51% Minority Group: A Statistical Essay; How to Discriminate agaist women Without Really Trying; Human Rights are Indivisible; The Legal Basis of the Sexual Caste System; Property of Mothers; Sexism and Social Science: From the Gilded Cage to the Iron Cage; The Social Construction of the Second Sex; The Women's Liberation Movemet: Its Origin, Structures and Ideas; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Fried, Morton H.; Mankind Excluding Women (1969); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Friedman, Deb and Lois Yankowski; Snuffing Sexual Violence (1976); Quest, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Gardner, Gerald H. F.; The Changing Role of Men in the Changing World of Woman (1970); The Status of Women in the Field of Computing (1970); Want-Ads Tomorrow: Neutral with Respect to Sex (1969); 1970, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Gardner, Jo-Ann E.; Autobiographical Notes Relevant to Sex Discrimination in Academic Psychology (1968); Sesame Street and Sex-Role Stereotypes; Sexist Counseling Must Stop (1971); What Effect Should the Femininst Movement Have on Higher Education?; Women: The World's Largest Oppressed Minority; KNOW, Inc., 1968-1971; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Garson, Barbara; The Bottle Baby Scandal: Milking the Third World for All It's Worth (1977); Mother Jones, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Gee, Emma; Issei: The First Women; Civil Rights Digest, Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Gipple, Cindy; The Women's Movement and the Class Struggle (1972); Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Goldberg, Marilyn; On Misandrism; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Goldfield, Evelyn, Sue Munaker and Heather Booth; Women in the Radical Movement, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Goodman, Ellen; Men's Liberation: An Effort at Understanding (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Gordon, Linda; Families (1970); The Fourth Mountain: Women in China; Towards A Radical Feminint History; Bread and Roses; New England Free Press; KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Gornick, Vivian; Women's Liberation: The Next Great Moment in History is Theirs (1969); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Greer, Germaine; Women's Lib on "FiringLine" with William F. Buckley, Jr. (1973); Playboy Interview, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Hanish, Carol and Elizabeth Sutherland; The Women's Rights Movement in the U.S.: A New View, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Ann Sutherland; The Second Sex in Academe (1970), Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Harris, Patricia Roberts; Remarks at the National Women's Political Caucas Convention, Cincinnati, Ohio (1979); HUD News, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Hartman, Sylvia; Princess Valium Meets Shrinkthink; Should Wives Work?; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Hartman, Sylvia; Princess Valium Meets Shrinkthink; Should Wives Work?; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Hawley, Andy; A Man's View (1969); Men's and Women's Liberation; KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Heide, Wilma Scott; A Feminist Manifesto: H.R. 11167 Employment and Manpower (SIC) Act of 1972; Human Rights are Indivisible; The Reality and Challenge of the Double Standard in Mental Health and Society; What's Wrong with Male-Dominated Society (1971); New York Times Guest Editorial; KNOW, Inc., 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Heide, Wilma Scott; A Feminist Manifesto: H.R. 11167 Employment and Manpower (SIC) Act of 1972; Human Rights are Indivisible; The Reality and Challenge of the Double Standard in Mental Health and Society; What's Wrong with Male-Dominated Society (1971); New York Times Guest Editorial; KNOW, Inc., 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Henley, Nancy; The American Way of Beauty; Facing Down the Man; Male Chauvinism Attitudes & Practices; The Politics of Touch (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Herman, Dianne; The Politics of Rape and Wifebeating: The Criminal Justice System's Response to Violence Against Women (1977), Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Hoddersen, Guerry; Revolutionary Feminism and the Class Struggle: President's Report to the Radical Women Annual Conference (1970);: Organizing Where We Work: Politics -- Not Tactical Recipes; Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Horner, Matina; A Bright Woman is caught in a double bind. In achievement-oriented situations she worries not only about failure but also about success (1969); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Howe, Florence; A Guide to Current Female Studies (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Jackson, Barbra; Marriage as Oppressive Institutions/Collectives as Solutions (1969); The Group, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Jacobs, Karen Folger; Venereal Disease, War, Sexism, and Racism (1972); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - James, Selma; Women, The Unions and Work, or, What is Not to be Done; "You Can't Make Ford Cars and Change Nappies at the Same Time": The Power of Women and Revolutionary Change (1973); Canadian Women's Educational Press, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Jones, Beverly; Toward a Female Liberation Movement; Toward a Strong and Effective Woman's Movement: The Chambersburg Paper; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Jones, Mother; Mother Jones in Appalachia [edited by Keith Dix]; Thoughts of Mother Jones, Compiled from her Writings and Speeches [edited by Jim Axelrod]; Appalachian Movement Press; Racial Education Project, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Jordan, Joan; The Place of American Women: Economic Exploitation of Women (1968); New England Free Press, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Joreen; The BITCH Manifesto; 51% Minoirty Goup: A Statistical Essay (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Kearon, Pamela; Man-Hating (1969); Power as a Function of the Group -- Some Notes (1969); Rules and Responsibility in a Leadership Feminist Revolutionary Group (1969); The Feminists, 1970; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Keiffer, Miriam G. and Dallas M. Cullen; Discrimination Experienced by Academic Female Psychologists (1969); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - King, Lourdes Miranda; Puertorriquenas in the United States: The Impact of Double Discrimination; Civil Rights Digest, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - King, Peggy and June Myers; Consciousness Raising; Washington, D.C. Chapter--NOW, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Koedt, Anne; The Myth of the Vaginal Orgasm (1970); Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Kollias, Karen; Sisterhood on Campus; NSA Women's Center, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Komisar, Lucy; Violence and the Masculine Mystique; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Kuang, Hsu, Tsui Yu-lan, Li Chen, Liu Chao, Hsing Yen-tzu, Feng Feng-Ying et al, and Lu Hsun; Women Hold Up Half the Sky; Peking Review and China Reconstructs, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Laws, Judith Long; The Social Psychology of Women: Shibboleths & Lacunae; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Leo, Evelyn; Oppression of Women Through Dependency in Marriage: Middle-Class Marriage Oppression (1970); The Group, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Leone, Vivien; Occupying the Ladies Home Journal: My First Hurrah (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Lesher, Margy; Choose Four: Lesbian/Feminist, Woman, Dyke, Gay, Chick, Homosexual, Lesbian, Amazon, Girl (1974); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    General
    Pittsburgh: KNOW Inc 1974. Handout 2 sheets stapled. From Lesbian Connection Vol. I no. 2 12/74. KNOW was a radical feminist Pittsburgh publishing collective.
  - Limpus, Laurel; Liberation of Women: Sexual Repression & the Family; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Lipneck, Jessica; Written with a Sunbeam: Women in the American Revolution, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Lockeretz, Sarah Wernick; Hernia: A Satire on Abortion Law Repeal; KNOW, Inc/, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Lowen, Marilyn; Women Can Liberate Themselves and Destroy Capitalism / Imperialism Too … yup; The New Women, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Lydon, Susan; Understanding Orgasm; D.C. Women's Liberation; reprint from Ramparts, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - MacLeod, Dianna and Rachel Bedard; Women in Community (1977); Movement for a New Society, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Mainardi, Pat; The Politics of Housework; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Mann, Nancy; Fucked-Up in America: A Response to "The Myth of the Vaginal Orgasm"; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Marjorie; Guilt in Women; The Group, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Martin, Del and Phyllis Lyon; Lesbians -- The Key to Women's Liberation; The Realities of Lesbianism (1969); D.C. Women's Liberation, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Martin, Gloria; Women in the American Revolutionary Struggle (1970); Seattle Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - McMillin, Nancy H.; Position Paper on Women (1969); University of Chicago, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Meeropol, Elli and Beth Schneider; The Ethel Rosenberg Story (1975); Philadelphia Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Mehrhof, Barbara; Class Structure in the Women's Movement (1969); The Rise of Man: The Origins of Woman's Oppression: One View (1970); The Feminists, 1969-1970; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Michaels, Sheila; The Archetypal Woman; The Feminists, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Mitchell, Juliet; Women: The Longest Revolution (1966); New England Free Press, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Moberg, Verne; Consciousness Razors; National Education Association, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Morgan, Robin; Goodbye to All That; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Morton, Laurie; The Feminist Movement and the Gay Movement (1975); Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Munaker, Sue; A Call for Women's Liberation (1968); The Resistance, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Myrdal, Gunnar; An American Dilemna; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Narek, Diane; A Woman Scientist Speaks (1969); Redstockings, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Nekvasil, Charles A.; Free the Women? (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - New Haven Women's Coalition Against Registration and the Draft; A Feminist Oppression to the Draft (1980); Yale Univ. Teach-In, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Nieto, Consuelo; The Chicana and the Women's Rights Movement: A Perspective; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Nikkalaos, Cordelia; People Power (1968); Mississippi Newsletter, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Noto, Lina; Man, This Hermaprodite [tranlated from Italian] (1974); International Feminists Task Force, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - O'Connor, Lynn; Male Supremacy, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - One, Varda; Manglish (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - Pfaehler, Phoebe and Lynn Leslie; Equality Road and Other Songs; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - Piercy, Marge; Grand Coolie Dam; The NSA Women's Center & New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - Pollard, Vickie and Donna Keck; They Almost Seized the Time!; Radical Education Project, Undated; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - Pompei, Giuliana; Wages for Housework (1972); Canadian Women's Educational Press, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - Pratt, Annis; Little Girl Sambo; The Want Ad Story; Know, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Pride, Anne; Feminist Entrepreneurs and the Women's Movement [1973); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Racz, Elizabeth; The Women's Rights Movement in the French Revolution (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Radical Women; Radical Women Manifesto: Theory, Program and Structure (1973); Revolutionary Socialist Feminists (1974); Sexual Politics; Why Independent Unions? (1975); Radical Women, 1973-1975; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Radicalesbians; The Woman Identified Woman (1970); Radicalesbians, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Randall, Margaret; Child Care in Cuba (1972); The Women's Press, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Rausch, A.; In Partial Payment: Class Struggle, Sexuality and the Gay Movement (1981); Sojourner Truth Organization, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Raymond, Jill; Socialist Feminism: Where Inner and Outer Needs Meet (1975); People's Party Resource Center, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Redstockings Sister, A; Brainwashing and Women: The Psychological Attack; Redstockings, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Evelyn; The Myth of Women's Inferiority; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Riddle, Dorothy; What the Doctors Forget to Tell You (or How to Survive Vaginal and Urinary Infections) (1971); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, Patricia; Poor Black Women, Including Birth Control Pills and Black Children; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Roche, Kathi; The Secretary: Capitalism's House Nigger; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Roodkowsky, Mary; Women and Hunger (March, 1976); American Friends Service Committee, 1976 March; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Ross, Loretta J.; Third World Women and Violence (1980); D.C. Rape Crisis Center, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Rossi, Alice S.; Discrimination and Demography Restrict Opportunities for Academic Women (1970); Job Discrimination and What Women Can Do About It (1970); Women in the Seventies: Problems and Possiblities (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Rush, Florence; The Florence Rush Reader (includes Who's Afraid of Margaret Ribble?], The Myth of Sexual Delinquency, Women in the Middle, Can Liberated Women Relate to Men?, The Sexual Abuse of Children] (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Russell, Diana E.H.; Pornography: A Feminist Perspective (June 1977), Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Russell, Valerie; Racism and Sexism, A Collective Struggle: A Minority Woman's Point of View (1970), Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Sawyer, Jack; The Male Liberation Movement (1970); On Male Liberation (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Schurr, Cathleen; Rape: Victim as Criminal (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Schwartz, Rosalind; Notes from the Woman Working Class: A Jewish Class Speaks Her Mind (1970); The Feminists, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Scott, Ann; The Half-Eaten Apple (1970); Feminism vs. the Feds (1971); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - SDS; SDS National Resolution on Women; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Seidenberg, Robert; Oedipus and Male Supremacy; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Shainess, Natalie, M.D.; Images of Woman: Past and Present, Overt and Obscured (1969); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Shelley, Martha; Gay is Good, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Shortridge, Kathleen; Women as University Nigger: How the 'U' Keeps Females in their Place (1970); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Sigal, Regina; Women and Contraception; Washington Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Socialist Labor Committee; Women March as the Family Crumbles; Socialist Labor Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Socialist Workers D.C. Campaign; Women's Liberation: a position paper; Socialist Workers Campaign, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Stannard, Una; Clothing and Sexuality (1971); The Male Maternal Instinct; What do you Think of Playboy?; KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 32)